飞出个未来
今天有考试
杀手级应用的崛起
Attack of the Killer App
作为市长 我深感乏味地宣布
As Mayor, it is my deeply tedious pleasure to kick off
第83或84届电子废物回收节开幕
the 83rd or 84th annual e-waste recycling festival!
前面的低头
Down in front!
抱歉 人群使我兴奋
Sorry. I get aroused in crowds.
现在 让我为仪式扔出第一件垃圾
I will now throw out the ceremonial first dump...
这台陈旧低效的投票操纵器
this old, inefficient vote rigger!
这些老旧的世界末日装置
These old doomsday devices are
极端危险地不稳定
dangerously unstable.
必须让它们不知所踪我才能安心
I'll rest easier not knowing where they are.
永别了 过于复杂的日式马桶
So long, overly complicated Japanese toilet.
请不要丢掉我
Please not to throw away.
我给了你快乐的便便时光
I give you happy poopie time.
抱歉 你知道得太多了
Sorry, you know too much.
看来这是一个摆脱证据的好地方
Seems like a good place to ditch some evidence.
掰弯仪
Flexo?!
你在危险废物箱里做什么
What are you doing in a hazardous waste bin?
你还没听说吗?
Haven't you heard?
我们掰弯机是危险的过期装置
Us bending units are dangerously outdated.
我们过热 有放射性
We overheat, we're radioactive,
还会导致勃起功能异...
we cause erectile dysfunc...
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
没人 你老妈
Your mama.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你自己选吧
Take your pick.
我是勺子·昌
Scoop Chang,
新纽约时报在线播客的评论编辑
New New York Times online podcast blog comments editor.
市长先生 这些电子废品有危险吗
Mr. Mayor, isn't this e-waste dangerous?
一点都不危险 勺子先生
Not at all, Scoop.
运到第三世界后就没危险
Not after it's hauled off to the third world
找一些低工资可牺牲的无名小卒运送就行
by an expendable team of minimum-wage nobodies.
好消息 无名小卒们
Good news, nobodies!
第三世界
天蝎座α星系
你们好 朋友们
Greetings, my friends!
拆光这架破机器花不了多少时间
It shan't take long to strip down your clunker.
我们的破机器没什么问题
There's nothing wrong with our clunker.
真的吗 可是我们嗅出了要人命的铬含量哦
Really? Because we can smelt out the deadly, deadly chromium
可以造老鼠药和甜味剂
to make rat poison and artificial sweeteners.
不 谢了 我们送的是电子垃圾
No, thanks. We're delivering e-waste.
真可惜 我们都完成一大半了
Pity. We're halfway done.
这玩意儿含百分之四十的铬
This thing is 40% chromium!
轻一点
Gentle now.
轻点推悬浮废料箱
Gentle with the hoverdumpster.
准备处理
Ready for processing!
什么闻起来一股鼻血味
What smells like bloody sinuses?
我们焚烧电子垃圾来提取可用金属
We burn your e-waste down to the usable metals,
毒气则安全地释放到
safely releasing the toxins
我们的大气和饮用水中
into our air and drinking water.
呃 这是我见过的最恶心的做法
Ugh! That's the worst thing I've ever seen!
真的吗 那你最好不要往那边看
Really? Then don't look over there.
好了 孩子们
Okay, kids.
我们来玩找闪闪
Let's play find the shiny!
这种做法更恶心
That's even more horrific!
所有的工作都让孩子来做吗
Is all the work done by children?
不 抽鞭子的不是
No, not the whipping.
我同意 我们后来也了解到一些回收的好处
Granted, we later learned some positive things about recycling,
但更好的解决办法是
but a better solution
尽可能延长电子产品的使用时间
is to use our electronics as long as possible
而不是从一开始就丢弃它
instead of throwing them out in the first place.
我要从留着我的旧手机开始
I'm gonna start by keeping my old cell phone,
尽管它过时了
even if it is outdated.
你好 特兰格小姐
Hello, Miss Turanga.
你拨到圣路易斯的电话已接通
Your call to Saint Louis has gone through.
那我们至少把这台电视扔掉
Well, let's at least throw this tv out.
遥控器的电量有点低了
The batteries in the remote are getting low.
不 把它放回去 打开
No! Put that back and turn it on!
我只是想帮忙
I was just trying to help.
在更多爆炸性新闻之前
More on this breaking puff-piece
我们的赞助商有句话要说
after a word from our sponsor.
用全新的EyePhone
With the new eyePhone,
你能看 能听
you can watch, listen,
疏离你的朋友 跟踪前男友
ignore your friends, stalk your ex,
在公交车上下载色情电影
download porno on a crowded bus,
甚至能一边被火车撞一边检查邮件
even check your e-mail while getting hit by a train.
尽在新EyePhone
All with the new eyePhone.
老妈公司
From Mom.
新的EyePhone
A new eyePhone?!
忘了这破烂好了
Forget this junk.
喂 这样的问候可真新鲜
Well, this is a fine how-do-you-do!
再见 撒哟拉那 拜拜
So long! - Sayonara! - Bye-bye!
可算摆脱了 没错 走你
Good riddance! - Yup! - Toodle-oo!
来吧 我们在线买些EyePhone吧
Come on, let's buy some eyePhones online.
等等 我以为我们要在线买EyePhones
Wait. I thought we were buying our eyePhones online.
我们就在线上
We are on line.
但我以为老妈店在城市另一头
But I thought the Mom store was across town.
它是在另一头
It is across town.
但是我以为
But I thought...
别再以为了 弗莱
Stop thinking, fry!
我感觉像一只无脑僵尸
I feel like a mindless zombie.
我真想知道我们等了多久
I wish I knew how long we've been waiting.
EyePhone有个应用程序能做到
The eyePhone has an app for that!
有亲我闪亮的屁股的程序吗
Is there an app for kissing my shiny metal ass?
有好几个
Several!
哦
Ooh!
噢不 有光
Oh, no, the light!
看来我的阳寿已尽
I guess I'm off to hell.
那只是商店的光 教授
That's the store, Professor.
哟啊
Whuh?
哇 是那种到处都能听到的
Swow! It's that obscure underground song
没人听得懂的地下歌曲
that's constantly playing everywhere.
亲爱的 你们好
Hello, dearies.
欢迎来老妈公司
Welcome to the Mom store.
新的EyePhones目前供不应求
The new eyePhones are in short supply,
所以请有秩序地...
so please form an orderly...
别挡道 我要...
Out of the way! - I need...
还有剩下的吗
Are there any left?!
可能有一个
There may be one.
好的 500美元
Okay, it's $500,
不能自主选择电信公司
you have no choice of carrier,
电池不能充电
the battery can't hold a charge,
接收效果不是很...
and the reception isn't very...
闭嘴 拿走我的钱
Shut up and take my money!
新的EyePhone非常棒
The new eyePhone is wonderful.
我用它来查食谱和发恐吓邮件
I use it to check recipes and send threatening e-mails
给未经授权的第三方应用程序开发者
to unauthorized third-party app developers...
我说 你在这家公司工作 你懂技术
Say, you're from one of those ethnicities that knows about technology.
它为什么叫EyePhone
Why is it called an eyePhone?
我装好它再解释
I'll explain after I install it.
好极了
Neat.
现在装听筒组件
Now for the ear piece.
但我最喜欢的应用程序是"推彻"
But my favorite app is called Twitcher.
噢
Ow!
推彻能让你收发短信息或小视频
Twitcher lets you send and receive short messages or videos
简称发推
called twits.
噢 现在就有人发推给我
Why, here's a twit now.
老妈 我对你的敬仰犹如...
Hi, mom. I love you more than can...
电量不足
Low battery.
但不必把我的话当真
But don't take my word for it.
无偏见老妈点评网说
Unbiased-reviews-dot-mom says
推彻是杀手级应用
Twitcher is the killer app.
当我说杀手应用时
And when I say killer app,
我的意思是杀手应用
I mean killer app!
现在 请看又一部下载剧集
And now another downloadisode of
模拟城市的真实主妇
the Real Housewives of Sim City.
她需要重置
She needs to reset.
我去跟她当面说
I'll say it to her face.
难怪传统媒体衰落了
No wonder traditional media is dead.
来看看摧眠蛙的网络剧集
Check out this webisode of Hypnotoad.
享受你过时的格式吧 老爷子
Enjoy your outdated format, grandpa.
如今像我这样的潮流青年
Nowadays, cool kids like me
都在合成我们自己的手机剧集
mash up our own phone-isodes.
是绑架者发来的
It's from the kidnappers.
我侄子还活着
My nephew is alive!
他就在...
And he's...
这个信封里
in this envelope.
他们切掉了我的一个维度
They cut off one of my dimensions!
不 不
No! No!
噢天哪 是班德
Oh, my God, it's Bender!
他会拯救大家
He'll save us!
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?
是青春期反应吗
Is it puberty?
这叫做来电 好像是
It's a phone call, dingus.
EyePhones也是电话
These eyePhones are phones, too?
废话
Duh.
弗莱在
Fry-lo.
嗨 弗莱
Hi, Fry.
你知不知道EyePhones也是电话
Did you know these eyePhones are phones, too?
废话
Duh.
嘿 你开船的时候打电话安全吗
Hey, is it safe to talk while you're flying?
哦 绝对安全
Oh, totally.
这东西是免提的
This thing's hands-free.
所以我才能一边吃玉米卷
That's how I can eat this taco.
一边吃意大利面
And this spaghetti.
我要挂了
I'm hanging up now.
嘿 看这个网络视频
Hey, check out this Internet video
某个笨蛋的飞船坠毁了
of some idiot crashing her spaceship!
你录了这个
You recorded that?
EyePhone什么都录
The eyePhone records everything.
我只是加了一点背景笑声
All I did was add a laugh track
然后推给我的一万粉丝而已
and twit it to my 10,000 followers.
噢 你提醒了我
Oh, that reminds me.
是时候推我的每小时更新了
It's time to my hourly twupdate.
粉丝们 你们好
'Sup, followers.
弗莱在此
Fry here.
打个鸡蛋嗝 挠个痒
Burping eggs, scratching my underarm fungus,
还在寻找爱
looking for love.
发送
Send.
腋下痒
Underarm fungus?
噢 信息量太大了
Ugh! Too much information.
这正是我想要的信息量
It's exactly the right amount of information!
多年来 我只能用传统方法收集个人资料
For years, I've collected personal data with old-fashioned methods,
比如木马程序和信息爬虫
like spybots and info-squitos.
这家伙还真喜欢黄片
This guy sure loves porno.
但现在
But now,
多亏了推彻
thanks to Twitcher,
这些傻瓜们自愿吐露
morons voluntarily spew out
所有我需要利用的信息
every fact I need to exploit them!
目标锁定了 老妈
Target acquired, mother.
启动直销算法
Fire direct marketing algorithm!
你是否正煎熬于...
Do you suffer from the heartbreak of...
我腋下的真菌
My underarm fungus.
那么先生/女士你....
Then you, Mr. or Mrs....
需要用老妈牌
Need the soothing relief
烧碱抗真菌漂白剂来舒缓
of mom's caustic anti-fungal bleach!
我能把帐记在EyePhone
Oh. Can I somehow charge it to my eyePhone
附加费用的上吗
for an additional fee?
当然可以
Hell, yes!
嘿 胖子 准备好大快朵颐
Hey, fatso, stuffa you face!
这玩意总是知道我何时需要小吃
This thing always seems to know when I got the munchies!
粉丝们注意
Attention followers.
今天街对面的批萨店配料免费
It's free topping day at the Pizza Place across the street!
发送
Send.
废话 所以我们上这儿来午餐了
Duh. That's why we all came over here for lunch.
发送
Send.
大家好 粉丝们
Greetings followers.
今天是我独自乘小艇环游世界的第五天
This is day five of my solo kayak journey around the world.
发送
Send.
你信不信居然有五万人相信我的鬼话
Can you believe 50,000 idiots swallow that crap?
发送
Send.
哎哟
Oops.
等等 你有五万粉丝
Wait. You have 50,000 followers?
我只有三个
I only have three.
发送
Send.
我昨天就取消关注了
I unsubscribed yesterday.
我有那么多粉丝是因为
I got the most followers 'cause
我给人们他们想要的
I give the people what they want.
比如你穿内裤练空手道的视频
Like this video of you doing karate in your underpants.
噢 救我 快叫警察
Ow! Help! Police!
发送
Send.
这太卑鄙了 班德 即使是以你的标准来说
That is low, Bender, even by your standards.
我的什么
My what now?
何时起 互联网成了滥用人们隐私的地方了
Since when is the Internet about robbing people of their privacy?
从它诞生的那天起
August 6, 1991.
我打赌我不用降低到你的水准
I'll bet I can get as many followers as you
我的粉丝也能像你的一样多
without sinking to your level.
你怎么说
What do you say?
赌一块钱看谁先获得一百万粉丝
First one to a million followers wins a buck.
赌就赌
You're on!
发送
Send.
输家有什么惩罚
What happens to the loser?
让我们玩得有趣点
Let's make it interesting.
恶心
Shplecch.
羊驼先生为什么这样子
Why is Mr. Chunks doing that?
因为赌输的人
Because the loser of our bet
必须空中转体两圈跳进外星羊的呕吐池里
has to do a double somersault into a tub of alien goat vomit.
等等 还有更有趣的
Wait, let's make it interestinger.
呕吐物和腹泄物
Vomit and diarrhea.
好主意
Good idea.
这样两边都不浪费
That way we don't waste an end.
呃 真恶心
Ugh, it's putrid.
你给它吃了什么
What do you feed him?
一张嘴里出来的喂给另一张嘴
What comes out one end, we feed to the other.
也喂印度菜
Also Indian food.
竞赛开始吧
Let the contest begin!
不可思议
Amazing.
有个蠢货有着将近一百万其他蠢货
Some dumb bastard has nearly a million other dumb bastards
在关注他的每条推
following his every twit!
你们这些蠢货在听我说吗
Are you dumb bastards listening to me,
愚蠢的混蛋们
you dumb bastards?
你为什么这么生气 老妈
Why are you so angry, mommy?
噢 抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
我只是对我的邪恶计划有点小紧张
I guess I'm just a little nervous about my evil plan.
你们这些蠢货
You dumb bastards!
你们看
You see,
这个计划将要进入第二阶段
the plan is about to enter phase two.
只要某人的粉丝达到一百万
As soon as someone reaches a million followers,
我就用他们来传播…
I'll use them to transmit...
推虫
The twit-worm.
老妈 你这个狡猾的巫婆
Oh, mother, you devious hag.
跟我们说说"推虫"的事吧
Tell us more about this "twit-worm."
这是一种特别的电脑病毒
It's a very special computer virus,
因为它不感染电脑
for instead of infecting computers,
而是感染人脑
it infects the human brain.
我喜欢
I like it.
百万粉丝将变成僵尸军队
The million followers will become an army of zombies,
渴望服从我的每一个指令
eager to obey my every command.
重点是 我们永远是一家人
The important thing is, we're a family.
不是
No, it's not!
恶心 他打喷嚏到里面了
Ew, he sneezed in it.
噢 老天 我要赌输了
Oh, God, I'm going to lose the bet.
我要在这吐我拉你胃液里游泳了
I'm gonna have to swim in the juice of the puke-me-poop-you.
别放弃
Don't give up.
你只需要发一些抓人眼球的推文
You just need more titillating twits.
相信我 我也想这么做
Trust me, I want twits that tittle.
那你就得降低到班德的水准
Then you're going to have to sink to Bender's level.
别装得像英国女王似的
Stop acting like the Queen of England.
那是谁 英国女王吗
Who was that... the Queen of England?
呃 失陪了
Uh, e... excuse me.
我必须...
I have to...
走了
someplace.
奇怪
That was odd.
歌声从哪儿来的
Where'd that singing come from?
不是那只羊
It wasn't the goat.
它的出口都在忙着
All of its orifices are in use.
♪ I dreamed a dream in time ♪
♪ gone by ♪
♪ when hope was high ♪
♪ and life worth living ♪
♪ I dreamed that love would never die ♪
♪ I dreamed that God would be ♪
♪ forgiving. ♪
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
没什么
Nothing.
我不是"没什么"
I'm not nothing.
我一生都被人叫做"没什么"
All my life everyone's called me nothing.
你屁股上有个脓包会跟你一起唱歌
You have a boil on your butt that sings show tunes with you?
别看着我
Don't look at me.
我是个怪物
I'm a freak.
不不 这个...
No, no... well...
在我的印象中我一直以苏珊为耻
Oh, I've been ashamed of Susan as long as I can remember.
你把你的脓包叫做苏珊
You named your boil Susan?
脓包不能有名字吗
A boil kinna have a name?
他们还说脓包不会唱歌呢
They also said a boil kinna sing,
但...
but...
♪ Amazing grace, how... ♪
啊
Aaah!
她还是苏格兰的
she's Scottish.
我每几个月就切开她
I lance her every few months,
但她总是会长回来
but she always grows back.
做独眼人已经够艰难的了
It's hard enough being a cyclops,
但如果有人发现苏珊
but if anyone found out about Susan,
我会垮掉的
I'd be devastated.
哇 恶心
Whoa, gross.
百万粉丝级别的恶心
Million-follower gross.
弗莱 删掉
Fry, delete that.
现在就删
Delete that right now!
什么
What?
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
在呕吐池里游泳真开心啊
So much for a pleasant swim in vomit.
发送
Send.
删掉了吗
Did you delete it?
呃
Eh.
谢谢你 弗莱
Thanks, Fry,
你是个很好的朋友
you're a good friend.
呃...
Eh...
嘿 就是她 真人出现了
Hey, there she goes in the genuine.
我们嘘她
Let's get to hooting.
嘘
Hoo!
哇啦啦
Whoa-oa-oas!
这不是网络第一红人吗
If it ain'ts the world's number ones Internet sensation!
哪儿
Where?
还有...什么
Also... what?
再放一遍
Play it one more time.
不 这是对丽拉的羞辱和贬损
No, it's humiliating and degrading to Leela.
再放十多次
Play it ten more times.
我就知道我不该把这个发到推上的
I know I shouldn't have twitted that,
但不去呕吐池里游一游难消我良心的不安
but not swimming in barf might ease my conscience.
但如果丽拉发现了
But if Leela should find out,
她会尊严扫地的
her dignity sac will rupture.
所以我们不能让她看见
That's why we can't let her see this.
丽拉锁上门 这样丽拉就不...
Leela, lock the door so Leela doesn't...
你怎么能这样对我
How could you do this?
可怜的羊驼先生
Poor Mr. Chunks.
至少他至死都在做他喜欢的事
At least he died doing what he loved.
现在他去了更好的地方
He's in a better place now.
我把一块普通板子做成了跳板
I turned a regular board into a diving board.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
即将发生的新闻 大伙儿
Impending news, everyone.
我们要知道谁赌赢了
We're about to learn the winner of the bet.
哦 天哪 天哪 天哪
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
我希望是我
I hope it's me.
等一下
Wait a minute.
我有可能输吗
There's a chance I could lose?
这不是交易的一部分
That wasn't part of the deal.
我的金斯顿的的乔治亚·布朗啊
Sweet Georgia Brown of Kingston Town.
是平局
It's a tie.
因为没有人输
Since no one lost,
所以谁也不用跳了
no one has to jump.
好啊 平局 我又赢了
All right, a tie! I win again!
我是个混球
Oh, I'm a scuzzball.
不要难过
Don't feel bad.
至少你不像丽拉那么惨
At least you're not Leela.
平局
A tie?
这结果比我预期的更好
This worked out better than I could have hoped.
现在我有二百万僵尸了
Now I'll have two million zombies.
实际上
Actually,
弗莱和班德可能有些共同的粉丝
Fry and Bender may share some of the same followers.
我们唯一能确定的是
All we can say for sure is that
我们会有一百万至二百万个僵尸
there will be between one million and two million zombies.
我能确定的是...
All I can say for sure is...
别等着吃耳光
Now, stop getting slapped
赶紧启动推虫
and power up the twit-worm.
既恶心又激动
It's both disgusting and inspiring,
像地铁里的杰瑞
like Jared from subway.
好吧
Okay,
就算我屁股上长了个会唱歌的包
I'm a freak with a singingutt boil,
但我或多或少也是人啊
but I'm still a human being, more or less.
会唱歌的屁股包
Singing butts boil?
那是昨天的新闻了
That's yesterdayses news.
就像那个在地铁里被大毛虫吃掉的杰瑞
Like that giant caterpillar what ate Jared from subway.
现在我们这些网虫又有了新的热门视频
Nows us Internet geeks gots a whole new video sensation.
那么说我的羞辱结束了
So my humiliation is over?
你谁啊
Who are you?
现在 用一百万到二百万僵尸
And now, to create an unstoppable army
建造一支势不可挡的军队
of between one and two million zombies.
呃 你不等到天气变好吗
Uh, shouldn't you wait for the weather to clear up?
不 我向你们呈献 推虫
No. I give you the twit-worm.
发送
Send.
啊 我厌倦了脑袋里老是有动静
Aah, I'm sick of my head doing things.
丽拉
Leela!
弗莱 我来找你谈谈
Fry, I came to talk to you.
不 我来找你谈谈
No, I came to talk to you.
看上去你好像只是坐在那里
It looked like you were just sitting there,
不过管它呢
but whatever.
我为我的所作所为感到非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry for what I did,
我知道我永远无法弥补你
and I know I can never make it up to you...
你不必道歉
You don't have to apologize.
其实我是来谢谢你
In fact, I came to thank you.
我以为你要打我
I think you mean hit me.
每个人都知道了我的秘密
Everyone knows my secret,
但没人在乎
but no one cares.
我没什么可隐瞒的了
I have nothing to hide anymore.
弗莱 谢谢你的自私和鲁莽
Oh, Fry, thanks to your selfish rudeness,
我现在已经如释重负了
a terrible weight has been lifted from my heart.
还有一个地方需要你释放一下重负
That's not the only place you need a terrible weight lifted.
苏珊和我都同意
Susan and I are agreed.
在我们生命中头一次
For the first time in our lives,
我们不用再以自己为耻
we're not ashamed of who we are.
我从没感到羞耻过
I was never ashamed.
过来
Come here.
什么这么臭
What stinks?
你在新泽西周围晃荡过吗
Were you rolling around in New Jersey?
丽拉 我知道我没法补偿你
Leela, I knew I could never make it up to you,
所以我退而求其次
so I did the next best thing...
我自己体会了一次我施与你的羞辱
I put myself through the same humiliation I put you through.
噢 你不必这么做的
Aw, you didn't have to do that.
不必吗 该死
I didn't? Damn.
到了明天 就没人会记得了
By tomorrow, no one will remember.
我能再抱抱吗
Can I have another hug?
不能
No.
捏着鼻子给他个机会吧
Oh, hold your nose and give it a go.
为你介绍全新的 EyePhone 2.0
Introducing the all new eyePhone 2.0
愚蠢的混蛋们
Damn bastards.